Wardha district, Maharashtra — 15 public health centres, 1,600 patients a day.
Every dot is a live facility health score. Two are in crisis.
Click a facility. HealthGrid doesn't just show data — it explains it.
Stock-outs in 2 days. Half the doctors absent. Patients up 36%.
The AI recommends a guarded stock transfer. One click to approve.
Executed as a live transaction — both facilities re-score instantly.
Ask the Health Copilot anything — English, हिंदी or मराठी.
It answers only from live district data — grounded, cited, actionable.
Now the frontline. A health worker picks their language…
…and simply speaks: "आज ओआरएस का स्टॉक 50 बचा है"
Gemini turns speech into a structured update — confirmed by the worker, never auto-applied.
No forms. No paperwork. No English required.
And the district command center reacts in seconds.
30-day projection: all 54 stock-out days prevented, zero new stock. HealthGrid AI.